[
    {
        "question": "あ",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "い",
        "answer": "i"
    },
    {
        "question": "う",
        "answer": "u"
    },
    {
        "question": "え",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "question": "お",
        "answer": "o"
    },
    {
        "question": "か",
        "answer": "ka"
    },
    {
        "question": "き",
        "answer": "ki"
    },
    {
        "question": "く",
        "answer": "ku"
    },
    {
        "question": "け",
        "answer": "ke"
    },
    {
        "question": "こ",
        "answer": "ko"
    },
    {
        "question": "さ",
        "answer": "sa"
    },
    {
        "question": "し",
        "answer": "shi"
    },
    {
        "question": "す",
        "answer": "su"
    },
    {
        "question": "せ",
        "answer": "se"
    },
    {
        "question": "そ",
        "answer": "so"
    }
]